Guide to the Robert Trent Jones papers, ca. 1924-2003.
Jones, Robert Trent papers
- Series II. Office Records
  - Financial Records [RESTRICTED]
    - Amex [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Amex miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - Amex Gold Card [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - Amex MW Victor [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Amex- G Doyle [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - Amex- Rulewich [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - RTJ Amex [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - Federal Expenses [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - First Union Bank [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - Florida Department of Revenue [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 19)
    - Florida Windstorm [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 20)
    - Fitzgerald, Joe [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - Florida Department of State [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - Fenwest and West, LLP [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - Florida Golf financial statements [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    - Vidabaun schedule [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 219, Folder 25)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Expenses [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - Ipswich - Minnotti [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Conveyance of Interests to Baldwin and Robert Trent Jones [RESTRICTED], 1967-1979 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Radice-Jones Joint Venture - Agreement and Related Papers [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Financials [RESTRICTED], 1965-1977 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Radice-Jones Joint Venture (1) [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Radice-Jones Joint Venture (2) [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Radice-Jones Joint Venture (3) [RESTRICTED], 1968-1975 (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Location Maps and Zoning By-Laws for PCD, includes some plans [RESTRICTED] (Box 249, Folder 9)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA - Fee to Radice [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 249, Folder 10)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA (1) [RESTRICTED], 1965-1966 (Box 249, Folder 11)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA (2) [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Box 249, Folder 12)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA (3) [RESTRICTED], 1966-1973 (Box 249, Folder 13)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA (4) [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 249, Folder 14)
    - Country Club of Ipswich, Ipswich, MA (5) [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 249, Folder 15)
    - Supervisor Expenses Ledger [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 301, Folder 25)
    - Golf Design (Guernsey) Ltd. - Accounts Receivable [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 301, Folder 26)
    - International Planners Ltd., Mountain Golf Developments Ltd., Amilroy Ltd., International Golf Developments Ltd., Algrave Atlantico Contrucao de Campos de Golf Ltd. Cash book [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 301, Folder 27)
  - Legal Affairs [RESTRICTED]
    - Coral Ridge ladies locker room plan [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Corporate resolutions [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Golf Developments, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Dr. Rene Young [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Coleman, Leonard and Morrison [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Breakwater Towers Apt. 908 [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Breakwater Towers Apt. 1161 [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Intercompany notes RTJ [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Fla Golf Corporation legal [RESTRICTED], 1968-1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Lake Mayan apartments [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Davie Property [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - RTJ Golf Corp [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Manassas expenses [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Notes [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Bill Waugh [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Pending Paula Correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Technical specifications [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Barbados- Pemberton Resorts [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Coral Ridge office materials [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Crumpin-Fox club [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Connelly Property maintenance, repairs [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Landlords notes- banks [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Gulfstream Bank [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Landlords Inc investments notes [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Merrill Lynch [RESTRICTED] (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Greenscape [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Robert Trent Jones National Golf Club, Prince William County, VA - Preliminary Surface Exploration and Geotechnical Engineering Study - Includes plan [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Broad Run, VA (2) [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Broad Run, VA - Jones and Lenahan [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Broad Run, VA [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Broad Run, VA [RESTRICTED], November -December 1985 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Broad Run, VA [RESTRICTED], January - October 1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Broad Run, VA [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - McClure Property, Prince William County, VA [RESTRICTED], 1974-1979 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Broad Run, VA - Robert Trent Jones and Jay Saunders Partnership Agreement Original [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Montrose Capital- 40,000 Acre Track, Virginia [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Montrose Capital- 40,000 Acre Track, Virginia [RESTRICTED], 1987-1998 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Lake Manassas, Manassas, VA [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Daily Contacts [RESTRICTED] (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Europe [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Filing [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Robert Trent Jones tax returns and financial statement [RESTRICTED], 1970s (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - RTJ International general corporate [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - RTJ foundation general corporate [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Florida Golf Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Ipswich Country Club litigation [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Permis de Constriure Modicatif Golf de Joyenval [RESTRICTED] (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Kate v. Jones (1) [RESTRICTED], 1989-1993 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Kate v. Jones (2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Kate v. Jones (3) [RESTRICTED], 1991-1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Ipswich - LeClair [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Ipswich - Bonito [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Ipswich - Carbone v. Eaton [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Ipswich Country Club - Eaton, Keating - List of Lawsuits [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Ipswich Country Club [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Ipswich Litigation Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1992-1995 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Ipswich Country Club - Lots Sold [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Bank for Savings v. Jones, et al [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Mike Goldberg [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Brox Industries v. Jones, Eaton Keating as Trustees [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Chick Lumber, Inc v. Eaton, Jones, Keating Weller, Trustees of CDC [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Huygens Dimella Shaffer and Associates v. Jones [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Jerome Construction Company v. Ipswich Country Club [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Roy Litigation [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Financial Information [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - First Eastern Bank (1) [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - First Eastern Bank (2) [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - First Eastern Bank (3 [RESTRICTED]), 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Stockley Park Project contracts, agreements, designs [RESTRICTED], 1980s (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Stockley Park Project correspondence [RESTRICTED] (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Stockley Park billings and payments [RESTRICTED] (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Lead Files, foreign miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Leads: Tanzania [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Leads: Scotland, Japan, England [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Leads: Columbia, China, Canada [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Leads: design proposals, requests. Negatives and affirmatives [RESTRICTED], 1990s (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Leads: New courses, information sheets [RESTRICTED] (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Anstalt leads files [RESTRICTED] (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Construction liens info [RESTRICTED] (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Singerling deposition [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Singerling deposition receipts and invoices [RESTRICTED], 1980s (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Singerling deposition: memos regarding stock certificates [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Singerling deposition exhibits [RESTRICTED] (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Singerling resume [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Fashion Cleaners documents [RESTRICTED], 1987-1990 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Singerling memorandum [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Singerling deposition exhibits [RESTRICTED], 1984-1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Singerling deposition file [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Singerling income tax return [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Singerling deposition notes [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Coral Ridge documents and invoices [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Singerling production [RESTRICTED], 1986-1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Coral Ridge financial statements, tax returns [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - American Golfers Club financial statements, tax returns [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Robert Trent Jones Corp. income tax returns [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Eagler Rock Checks [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Documents Produced by David Williams [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Singerling documents produced for investigation [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Singerling: production from Chandross accounting records [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Jones Investigation: Coral Ridge Member List [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Singerling: Tapes from meeting with Wasser [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Jones and Singerling intervies [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Singerling Case: Board of Nursing [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Singerling: Point O'Woods [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Singerling: First Union [RESTRICTED], 1988-1991 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Singerling: Escape Travels [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Club Managers Association yearbook [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Singerling Files [RESTRICTED] (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Armstrong deposition [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Robert Trent Jones - Europe, Golf Developments Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Ione Jones Estate [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Ione Jones Estate, Mortmain Proceedings [RESTRICTED], 1987-1989 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Revocable Trust Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Guardianship of Grandchildren [RESTRICTED], 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Robert Trent Jones inc, Mortmain Settlement Proceedings, Trust Litigation [RESTRICTED], 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Singerling/Jones financial statements [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Singerling investigation Stafford binder [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Wasser investigation reports [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Singerling petition for dissolution of marriage [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Singerling case Stafford working documents [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Broward Paint and Wallpaper Co. production file [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Designer plumbing production file [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Subfile Rachlin and Cohen [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Memo and employment agreement [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Deposition file: Gordon Robert [RESTRICTED]s, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Deposition file: Kenneth Brown [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Deposition file: Michael Newell [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Deposition file: Dwayne Dale Dougla [RESTRICTED]s (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Deposition file: Ellen Ricci [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Deposition file: Ron Sharp [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Deposition file: Rees Lee Jones [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Deposition file: Harold Bowers [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Deposition file: Carlisle Depo [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Deposition file: Robert Trent Jones [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Deposition file: Russell Carlisle Esq. [RESTRICTED] (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Ipswich Elk Associates [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Ipswich Country Club [RESTRICTED], 1970-1974 (Box 151, Folder 2-3)
    - Acquisition and Finances of premises in Ipswich and Rowley [RESTRICTED] (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Ipswich Country Club [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Radice Realty and Construction [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Ipswich feasibility study [RESTRICTED] (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Ipswich [RESTRICTED], 1967-1979 (Box 151, Folder 8-9)
    - SSAAG Stock to RTJ for fees [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - From Antwerp, Elshoutheide [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 152, Folder 2-5)
    - Erosion Land Company Stock and transfer ledger, stock certificates [RESTRICTED], 1957 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Stocks, ledgers, Lackawanna Engineering Company [RESTRICTED] (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Turf Irrigation, Inc stocks and ledgers [RESTRICTED] (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - RTJ miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 219, Folder 26)
    - Gianola, Giorgio [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Jones personal [RESTRICTED], 1990-1993 (Box 219, Folder 28)
    - Trial Balances [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 219, Folder 29-33)
    - Rulewich, Roger [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Box 219, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 219, Folder 35)
    - Payable- American National Bank [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 36)
    - RTJ Year End [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 219, Folder 37)
    - RTJ International irrigation [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 38)
    - Kajima/Anglebrook change orders [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Box 219, Folder 39)
    - Phillips and Jordan, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 219, Folder 40)
    - Smith Mountain Lake [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 219, Folder 41)
    - Robert Trent Jones miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box 219, Folder 42)
    - State Certificate, Alabama [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 219, Folder 43)
    - Sunbank statements [RESTRICTED], 1980s (Box 219, Folder 44)
    - Account ledgers [RESTRICTED], 1972-1982 (Box 219, Folder 45)
    - Planned Communities Inc. (5) [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Planned Communities Inc. (6) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Planned Communities Inc. (7) [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Planned Communities Inc. (8) - Bank Statements [RESTRICTED], 1975-1982 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Planned Communities Inc. - Reports and Plans [RESTRICTED] (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Planned Communities Inc. - Chiles Property Fairfax C., VA [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Planned Communities Inc. - Purchase Country Club, Rye, NY [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - Planned Communities Inc. - Purchase Country Club and Rye, NY - Plans [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Related Companies
    - Manager's Duties - Coral Ridge, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Menus - Coral Ridge, 1964-1966 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1965 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Palm Bay Club, 1965-1968 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Pargo - Carts, 1957-1962 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Parties, 1962-1965 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Patio Plan - Coral Ridge, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Pictures (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Pro Shop - Coral Ridge, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Publicity and Promotion - Coral Ridge, 1963-1965 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Ranger, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - The Ridge Rider, 1963-1969 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Rules - Guides to make rules, 1963-1967 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Salaries (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Schmeisser, John, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Score Cards, 1964-1966 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Security, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Septic Tanks, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Shoe Shining, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Signs, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - Shopping Center (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - Social Events, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Staff Meetings, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Straith, Dee, 1965-1967 (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - Swimming Pool Information, 1961-1963 (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Tamarac, 1963-1966 (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - Taxes [RESTRICTED], 1955-1965 (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Telephones, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - Tennis, 1962-1967 (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Tips, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 31)
    - Tournaments, 1962-1971 (Box 127, Folder 32)
    - Urban Land Institute, 1960 (Box 127, Folder 33)
    - Vacations (Box 127, Folder 34)
    - Waitress Information (Box 127, Folder 35)
    - Wells College - Florida, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 36)
    - Wells Landscape Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 127, Folder 37)
    - Wells, Pat, 1965-1966 (Box 127, Folder 38)
    - Well Water, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 39)
    - Widows (Box 127, Folder 40)
    - Wines, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 41)
    - Women's Southern Golf Association - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 127, Folder 42)
    - Worsham, Lew, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 43)
    - Federal Golf Inc., 1954-1984 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Florida General, continuing current, 1980-1982 (Box 156, Folder 2-3)
    - Florida Corporations, general, 1970-1981 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Florida Corporations minutes, unsigned, 1981-1982 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Florida by-laws and articles (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Florida Hoos-Richardt (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Florida Properties Appraisals, 1972 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - General, 1961-1972 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Controller (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Georgia Athens, Simpson Lane, 1964-1966 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - GDI St. Louis, 1970 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Golf Course Financing, 1963 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Donald Hobart, 1974 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Golf Challenge, 1969-1973 (Box 156, Folder 15-17)
    - Coral Ridge Golf Course, 1966-1985 (Box 159, Folder 1-4)
    - Lake Mayon Apt., 1964 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Broward County Assessments, 1981 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Coral Ridge JM Acquisition (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Coral Ridge Fence, 1970-1972 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Coral Ridge Memos (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Breakwater Towers, 1971-1985 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Florida New system (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - Cotton Bay properties limited, 1963-1969 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - Cotton Bay Trust Corporation Limited (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - John Dellis, Inc. (Box 159, Folder 14-1516-17)
    - Den Golf, Inc. (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - Hale and Prietsch reports, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Golf Public Relations, 1974-1977 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - International Contractors Ltd. (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Bahama Islands Memorandum and Articles of Association, 1966, 1968 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Half Moon Rose Hall agreements (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Golf Ridge Construction Co. (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - RTJ Great Golf Stories book material, 1982-1983 (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Hanen project, 1980-1984 (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Hertz suit, 1977 (Box 161, Folder 9)
    - Conveyance of Country Club of North Carolina Property to RTJ, 1979 (Box 161, Folder 10)
    - Robert Farwick, 1981 (Box 161, Folder 11)
    - Ficken, Henry and Cecile, 1964 (Box 161, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Corporations (Box 161, Folder 13)
    - East Valley Ranch (Box 161, Folder 14)
    - Erickson Injury, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 15)
    - Martin Cohen (Box 161, Folder 16)
    - Critical Path Methods (Box 161, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964-1968 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Robert Trent Jones and Associates Limited, 1959-1971 (Box 169, Folder 2-5)
    - RTJ Television Special, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Ione D. Jones Medical Claims and payments, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - RTJ Accounts and billings, 19 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Ridgewood Industries (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - RTJ Inc. Lease, Palo Alto, 1961-1975 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - RTJ of California (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Maurice Jospe, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Kingston taxes [RESTRICTED] (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Kansas Golf Construction, Inc. (Box 169, Folder 14-15)
    - Land Erosion Inc (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Lackawanna Engineering Inc. (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Landscape Architects Contract for services of RTJ (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Lake hazeltine (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Land Development Co., 1964 (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Legends of Golf, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Management Services, 1985 (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Andy Merlo, 1977 (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - The House of Lloyd (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - General miscellaneous projects, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 25)
    - Landlords conveyance from land planners, 1965 (Box 169, Folder 26)
    - Mistretta Pine Valley Park (Box 169, Folder 27)
    - Dick Morrison (Box 169, Folder 28)
    - NJ Corporations, general, 1965 (Box 169, Folder 29)
    - Northlake Construction Co. (Box 169, Folder 30-31)
    - Agresearch, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - American Golf Course Construction, 1964-1983 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - American Golfer, Inc., 1957-1966 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - The American Golfer's Club, Inc., 1957-1980 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - The American Golfer's Club, Inc., 1960-1978 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Licensing of "Architects", 1962 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Aquamatic, S.A. (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Art Mechanical Contractors, Inc., 1974-1984 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Automated Statements Inc. of Florida, 1969-1974 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Autogation, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Bahama Islands Developments, Ltd., 1960-1976 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Barclay's Bank, 1965-1969 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Bermuda, S.A., 1972 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Brau Boat, 1965-1966 (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Baldwin, William D., 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Lucille Baldin Estate, 1978-1979 (Box 236, Folder 16)
    - Cage, 1967-1971 (Box 236, Folder 17)
    - Calgolf, Inc., 1962-1984 (Box 236, Folder 18)
    - Calgolf, Inc., 1964-1978 (Box 236, Folder 19)
    - California Corporations - General, 1964-1985 (Box 236, Folder 20)
    - Carolina Trace Corporation, 1970-1982 (Box 236, Folder 21)
    - Club Services, Inc., 1967-1974 (Box 236, Folder 22)
    - Club Services, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 236, Folder 23)
    - Club Services, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 236, Folder 24)
- Series III. Project Records
  - Project files
    - Greenwich Municipal Golf Course, Greenwich, CT, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Greenwich Municipal Golf Course, Greenwich, CT, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Greenwich Municipal Golf Course, Greenwich, CT, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)